Guide to the Gotham Inc. Records, 1967-1997 and undated RL.00468
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Gotham Inc. records
1967-1997 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Gotham, Inc.
RL.00468
113.5 Linear Feet
The Gotham Inc. advertising agency was established by the Interpublic Group in 1994 as an independent agency of the global marketing services holding company. Gotham Inc. is one of New York's leading integrated communication agencies. The Gotham Inc. Records contain primarily video and print advertisements created for clients by Gotham's predecessor companies Daniel & Charles and Laurence, and Charles, Free & Lawson. The materials span 1967-1997 and include videocassettes, slides, magazine and newspaper advertisements, and memorabilia as well as agency brochures and limited general information. Clients represented in the collection include: Bristol-Myers (Ban, Bufferin, Comtrex); Clairol (Herbal Essence, Infusium); Dial; Drackett (Endust, Renuzit, Vanish); GAF Corporation; Ross Laboratories (Ensure, Selsun Blue); Thompson Medical (Cortizone, Dexatrim); and American Home Food Products. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
5000 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Gotham Inc. Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1998.
Historical Note
Since its inception, Gotham Inc. has been characterized in corporate literature as one of the first New Wave creative agencies that rides the cutting edge of advertising by hiring novice professionals who are driven by instinct and not afraid to try new approaches. Gotham Inc.'s self-described philosophy is disciplined creativity which refers to a blend of maverick creativity, rigorous research, and carefully developed marketing strategies. Gotham's basic creative strategy is to present an advertising concept in a variety of ways rather than constant repetition of a single advertisement. Gotham Inc. has a strong record for starting with single products and winning over additional products lines from the same parent company. Radio and television broadcast advertising represent their largest advertising format.
Source: Gotham Inc. website, company prospectus.
Chronology List
1952 Daniel & Charles (D&C) founded by Charles Goldsmith and Daniel Karsch
1963 Larry Dunst joins D&C as a copy writer.
1967 Larry Dunst named head of the Creative Department and a Senior Vice President at D&C. At 25 years old, Dunst is identified in company promotions as a member of the New Wave of young creative sparks which were infusing fresh energy and new talent into the advertising world.
1969 Dunst named President of D&C, the youngest head of a major advertising agency. Under his leadership the agency grows competitive with the larger agencies, and wins clients from JWT, McCann-Erickson, Ogilvy & Mather, and others.
1969 F. William Free & Company founded by F. William Free.
1972 D&C is sold to Mickelberry Corporation, an investment holding company listed on the New York Stock Exchange. D&C operates as an independent subsidiary.
1980 D&C acquires the Bufferin account as a result of its successful campaigns for Comtrex and Ban Roll-On, two other accounts Daniel & Charles handled for Bristol-Meyers.
1981 D&C acquires F. William Free & Company to form Laurence, Charles, & Free (LC&F). Daniel Karsch leaves Gotham to become Executive Vice President of Creamer, Inc. Charles Goldsmith (former chair of D&C) named chair. The merger brings together American Tobacco products Tareyton (D&C), Lucky Strike (D&C), and Carlton (Free); and forces the agency to resign from D&C’s Schenley Industries (Ancient Age, Canadian, DeBouchette, etc.) account in favor of Free’s Heublein account (Black Velvet, Jose Cuervo, etc.). Free also acquires accounts from Adidas, Alfa Romeo, and Coca Cola Foods (Active Yogurt).
1985 Ad Age ranks LC&F as the 17th largest agency on the East Coast and 43rd in the US.
1986 Tom Lawson joins LC&F and the name changes to Laurence, Charles, Free & Lawson (LCF&L). Offices in New York, N.Y.; Bloomfield Hills, Mich.; and Milwaukee, Wisc.
1994 Gotham Inc. founded.
Collection Overview
The Gotham Inc. Records contain primarily video and print advertisements created for clients by Gotham's predecessor companies (Daniel & Charles, and Laurence, Charles, Free & Lawson). The materials span 1967-1997 and include videocassettes, slides, magazine and newspaper advertisements, and memorabilia as well as agency brochures and information. Clients represented in the collection include: Bristol-Myers (Ban, Bufferin, Comtrex); Clairol (Herbal Essence, Infusium); Dial; Drackett (Endust, Renuzit, Vanish); GAF Corporation; Ross Laboratories (Ensure, Selsun Blue) Thompson Medical (Cortizone, Dexatrim); and American Home Food Products.
Collection Arrangement
The Collection is arranged into four series by type of material: Audiovisual Materials, organized alphabetically by client and product; Slides and Memorabilia, arranged alphabetically by product; Print Advertisements, organized alphabetically by product into two subseries according to size; and Agency Information relating to Gotham predecessor companies Daniel & Charles, and Laurence Charles & Free.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
J. Walter Thompson Company. Advertising Vertical Files, 1950-1994
Wells Rich Greene Inc. Records, 1954-1998 and undated
Jim Brown Papers, 1945-1959 and undated
Lore Parker Papers, 1950-1979 and undated
Videocassettes; Photographs; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Television commercials -- United States; Slides (photographs); Bristol-Myers Company; Clairol, inc.; Daniel & Charles (Firm); GAF Corporation; Drackett Company; Interpublic Group of Companies; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Gotham, Inc.; Laurence, Charles, Free & Lawson (Firm); Gotham, Inc.; Ross Laboratories
- Audiovisual Materials, 1973-1996 and undated, 129 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Contains audiovisual materials organized by client and product alphabetically. Item descriptions reflect information included on or with the materials and is recorded here as it appeared on the originals. A running number has been added to the individual items to aid in the identification of materials for the creation of use copies.
  - Major Clients, 1973-1996 and undated
    - Bristol Myers, 1973-1996 and undated
      - Ban, 1973-1975 (Box 1)
        - 1. Daniel and Charles. Ultra Ban Spray. 7 Days a Week. :30. 1975 (Box 1)
        - 2. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Lotion. BRUM 5163 Lotion Lover Rev. :30. 1975 (Box 1)
        - 3. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Super Dry. BMSD 5143 3X3 Rev. :30. 1975 (Box 1)
        - 4. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Super Dry. BMSD 5133 3 & 3. :30. 1975 (Box 1)
        - 5. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Super Dry. BMSD 5113 White/NO Z. :30; BMSD 5123 Black/NO Z. :30. 1975 (Box 1)
        - 6. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Super Dry. BMSD 5103 TV White Spanish Version :30. 1975 (Box 1)
        - 7. Bristol-Myers. Ban Basic. BMBB 5053 Sonoma/Cooney :30. 1975 (Box 1)
        - 8. Bristol-Myers. Ban Basic. Sonoma Candid :60; Sonoma Annc'r. :60. Undated (Box 1)
        - 9. Bristol-Myers. Ban Basic. BMBB 5043 Sonoma/Lamke :30; BMBB 5066 Sonoma/Annc'r Rev. :60; BMBB 5076 Sonoma/Candid Rev. :60. 1975 (Box 1)
        - 10. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban 5000. BMUB 4863 No Zirconium :30. 1974 (Box 1)
        - 11. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban. BMUB 4823 McQueen; BMUB 4833 Knight; BMUB 4843 Wynne. Undated (Box 1)
        - 12. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban 5000. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1974 (Box 1)
        - 13. Daniel and Charles. Ultra Ban Super Dry. BMSD 4093 TV-Black :30; BMSD 4083 TV-White :30. 1974 (Box 1)
        - 14. W-V. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Lotion. BMUR 4093 Listen :30. 1974 (Box 1)
        - 15. DMC Films. Ultra Ban 500.. 1973 (Box 1)
      - Ban (continued), 1976 (Box 2)
        - 16. Daniel and Charles. Ban Basic. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 17. Ban Basic. 7 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 18. Ban Basic. Sonoma/Candid Rev. #2. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 19. Daniel and Charles. Ban Basic. BMBB 6513 Gibbons/Rev. :30; BMBB 6523 Bongi/Rev. :30. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 20. Daniel and Charles. Ban Basic. BMBB 6443 Candid/Gibbons; BMBB 6453 Candid/Bongi.. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 21. Daniel and Charles. Ban Basic. BMBB 6423 Spokesman S&D/Rev.. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 22. Daniel and Charles. Ban Basic. BMBB 6413 25 cent Offer/Rev. :30. Undated (Box 2)
        - 23. Ban Basic. BMBB 6333 Tabletop/SD. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 24. Ban Basic. BMBB 6303 Stopped. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 25. Ban Basic. BMBB 6293 Tabletop. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 26. Daniel and Charles. B-M. Ultra Ban Lotion. BMUR 6283 Camera :30. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 27. Bristol-Myers. Ban Basic. BMBB 6216 League City/Hardin Rev. :60; BMBB 6223 League City/Annc'r Rev. :30. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 28. Bristol Myers. Ban Basic. BMBB 6146 League City/Hardin :60; BMBB 6133 League City/Annc'r :30; BMBB 6153 League City/Candid :30. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 29. Bristol Myers. Ban Basic. BMBB 6193 Sonoma Lamke Rev. :30; BMBB 6203 Sonoma Cooney Rev. :30; BMBB 6186 Sonoma Annc'r Rev. 2 :60. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 30. Bristol-Myers. Ban Basic. BMBB 6086 Stowe/Aerial :60; BMBB Stowe/Candid :30; BMBB Stowe/Annc'r :30. 1976 (Box 2)
        - 31. Daniel and Charles. B-M. Ban Super Solid. BMbr 6023 Vignettes :30. 1976 (Box 2)
      - Ban (continued), 1977-1978 (Box 3)
        - 32. Daniel and Charles. Ban Basic. BMBB 7933 Newspaper: 30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 33. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Basic. BMBB 7843 Answer/Hoche :30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 34. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban II. BMUB 7113 Balloon/Wash :30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 35. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Basic. BMBB 7023 Birdhouse :30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 36. D&C. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban II. BMUB 7163 American Rev. :30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 37. Daniel and Charles. Ultra Ban II. BMUB 7073 Newspaper Date 11 :30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 38. Bristol-Myers. Ban Basic. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 39. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban II. BMUB 7053 Balloon Rev. :30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 40. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban II. BMUB 7103 Balloon II Rev. :30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 41. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban II. BMUB 7013 Balloon :30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 42. Ban Basic. FA# 768. Directional Gordon ALT.. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 43. Daniel And Charles. Ban Basic. BMBB 7983 :30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 44. Winkler. Ultra Ban. BMUB 7153 America :30. 1977 (Box 3)
        - 45. Daniel and Charles. Ban. BMUB 8323 Thunder :30. 1978 (Box 3)
        - 46. Daniel and Charles. Ultra Ban II. BMUB 8265 Sure Can't :30. 1978 (Box 3)
      - Ban (continued), 1978-1979 (Box 4)
        - 47. Daniel and Charles. Ultra Ban II. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 48. Daniel and Charles. Ultra Ban II Umbrella/No Rain :30. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 49. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban II. Demo; Ultra Ban Lotion. Toughest Job. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 50. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Basic. BMBB 8043 Breath :30. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 51. Daniel and Charles. Ultra Ban II. Couple With Two Different Cores. 3/4 in. Video Cassette. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 52. Daniel and Charles. Ban Big Ball Roll On. BMUB 8063 Results :30. Undated (Box 4)
        - 53. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban II. BMUB 8323 Umbrella: In the Rain; BMUB 8333 Umbrella: Sliding Panels; BMUB 8343 Umbrella: Two Umbrellas. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 54. Ultra Ban II. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 55. Daniel and Charles. Ultra Ban II. Formula :30. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 56. Daniel and Charles. Ultra Ban II. Umbrella/No Rain :30. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 57. Bristol-Myers. Big Ban Ball Roll On. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 58. Daniel and Charles. Ban Presentation Reel. Good Better; Sliding Panels; Step By Step. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 59. Daniel and Charles. Ban. BMUB 8333 Sliding Panel :30. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 60. Daniel and Charles. Ultra Ban II. Couples 2 spots. R-11 PUB Coded. 05:26. 1978 (Box 4)
        - 61. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Line. BMUL 9583 You Don't Stop Rev. :30. 1979 (Box 4)
        - 62. Ban Dry Action. BMDA 9013 Hammock. 1979 (Box 4)
      - Ban (continued), 1979 (Box 5)
        - 63. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Soap. BMBC 9073 Feels Terrific :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 64. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Soap. BMBC 9123 Feels Terrific Rev. II. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 65. Daniel and Charles. Ban. Hammock Dry Action :30; Hammock Results :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 66. Daniel and Charles. Ban Dry Action. BMDA 9013 Hammock Vers. III :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 67. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Deodorant Soap. BMBC 9073 Looks Terrific :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 68. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Super Solid. BMBR 9073 Two Kinds :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 69. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Line/Ban Soap. BMUL 9533 Umbrella Dual; BMBC 9073 Looks Terrific; BMUL 9543 Umbrella/Roll On/ Spray. A roll/2 Scenes :30/. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 70. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Soap. BMCB 9133 Feels Terrific III :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 71. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Super Solid. BMBR 9063 Rally :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 72. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Dry Action. Hammock. Revised Copy III :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 73. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Soap. BMBC 9093 Feels Terrific Rev. :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 74. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Dry Action. BMDA 9013 Hammock :30. Alternate End. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 75. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Soap. BMBC 9213 Stephanie :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 76. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban II. BMUB 9383 First Name Dual :30. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 77. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Dry Action. BMDA 9013 Hammock :30. Revised Copy. 1979 (Box 5)
        - 78. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Dry Action. Hammock Rev. Copy II :30. 1979 (Box 5)
      - Ban (continued), 1980-1981 (Box 6)
        - 79. Bristol-Myers. Dry Action. BMDC 9023 Hammock Dry Action :30. Undated (Box 6)
        - 80. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Soap. BMBC 9103 Country Girl :30. Undated (Box 6)
        - 81. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Soap. BMBC 9103 Country Girl :30. Undated (Box 6)
        - 82. Ban Soap. 7-30 Sec. Spots. 1980 (Box 6)
        - 83. Bristol-Myers. Ban Historical Reel. 19-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1980 (Box 6)
        - 84. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Defense Power. BMSQ 0113 Defense :30. 1980 (Box 6)
        - 85. Ban Soap. 2-30 Sec. 2 Spots. 1980 (Box 6)
        - 86. Daniel and Charles. Ban-Animatics. Toughest Man; Tennis; Shirts. 1980 (Box 6)
        - 87. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Soap. BMBC 9143 Thanks Bob :30; BMBC 9153 Who Did It :30. 1980 (Box 6)
        - 88. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ban Soap. BMBC 9213 Stephanie :30. 1980 (Box 6)
        - 89. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Dry Action. BMDC 0063 His & Hers :30. 1980 (Box 6)
        - 90. Bristol-Myers. Ban. Historical Reel. 26 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1980 (Box 6)
        - 91. Daniel and Charles. Ban Animatics. Antique Dress; This Blouse. 1981 (Box 6)
        - 92. Bristol-Myers. Ban Roll On presentation. 1981 (Box 6)
        - 93. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Solid. ULT 1412. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1981 (Box 6)
        - 94. Daniel and Charles. Bristol-Myers. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1981 (Box 6)
      - Ban (continued), 1982-1984 (Box 7)
        - 95. LCF Bristol-Myers. Ban Roll On. BMBA 2033 Ban Version I :30. 1982 (Box 7)
        - 96. LCF. Ban Roll On. Mother Daughter Rev. :30; BMBA 2033 Ban Version 2 :30. 1982 (Box 7)
        - 97. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Roll On. BMUB 1702 Volt Ball/Niles :20. 1982 (Box 7)
        - 98. Ultra Ban. Historical Reel, 1971-1982. 46-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1982 (Box 7)
        - 99. Bristol-Myers. Ban Roll On. BMBA 2053 Columnist Note Par :30. 1982 (Box 7)
        - 100. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ultra Ban Solid. BMUS 2803 Mr. Connors Rev. 1 :30. 1982 (Box 7)
        - 101. Ban Roll On. Animatic Reel D. BMBA 3183 Testing Grounds Rev.; BMBA 3173 First Thing I Put On Rev.; BMBA 3163 Hidden Camera Rev.. 1983 (Box 7)
        - 102. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Roll On. BMBA 3163 Hidden Camera Rev. 1983 (Box 7)
        - 103. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Roll On. BMBA 3133 Ban & Sportswear/New Core :30. 1983 (Box 7)
        - 104. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Roll On. BMBA 3133 Ban & Sportswear/New Core :30. 1983 (Box 7)
        - 105. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Roll On. BMBA 3143 Ban And Sportswear Vers. 2 :30. 1983 (Box 7)
        - 106. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Roll On. BMBA 3133 Ban & Sportswear/New Core :30. 1983 (Box 7)
        - 107. Ban. Presentation Reel. 9 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1984 (Box 7)
        - 108. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Roll On. Historical Reel, 1970-1983. 24-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1983 (Box 7)
        - 109. Laurence Charles & Free. Ban. BMBA 3133 Ban And Sportswear/New Core :30. 1984 (Box 7)
        - 110. Ban. Presentation Reel. 9 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1984 (Box 7)
        - 111. Laurence Charles & Free. Ultra Ban Solid. Ultra Ban Solid Rev. :30. 1983 (Box 7)
      - Ban (continued), 1988 (Box 8)
        - 112. Laurence Charles & Free. Ban Spray. 14 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 113. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMBQ 8103 Towel :30. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 114. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Line. BMLN 8013 Memories/Coupon Tag :30. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 115. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Line. BMLN 8013 Memories/Coupon Tag :30. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 116. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMBQ 8103 Towel :30. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 117. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Aerosol. BMIC 8055 All Vignette :15. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 118. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Aerosol. BMIC 8055 All Vignette :15. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 119. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMBQ 8103 Towel :30. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 120. Laurence Charles & Free. Bristol-Myers. Ban Aerosol. BMIC 8055 All Vignette :15. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 121. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMBQ 8043 Towel Animatic. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 122. Ban Wagon. Dailies. Swipes. Shower/People Scenery/Chrome. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 123. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. BMIC 8085 All Vignette Alt. :15. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 124. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Aerosol. BMIC 8073 Psst FSI Tag :30. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 125. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMBQ 8163 Towel shower Head Intro :30. Bars and Slate. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 126. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMBQ 8063 Into The Night/Chanting :30. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 127. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Aerosol. BMIC 8023 Psst/Intercut :30; Ban Solid. BMBQ 8163 Solid/Towel/Shower Head Intro :30. 1988 (Box 8)
        - 128. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMBQ 8103 Towel :30. 1988 (Box 8)
      - Ban (continued), 1988-1989 (Box 9)
        - 129. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 9)
        - 130. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Aerosol. BMIC 9105 Aerosol/Flutter Cut Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 131. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Wide Solid. BMRX 9025 Wide Solid Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 132. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban. BMIC 9105 Aerosol/Flutter Cut Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 133. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Wide Solid. BMRX 9025 Wide Solid Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 134. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMBQ 8195 Vignette Alt. Rev. 1 :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 135. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Line. BMLN 9073 Line/Flutter Cut Rev. :30. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 136. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMBQ 8195 Vignette Alt. Rev. 1 :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 137. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Wide Solid. BMRX 9025 Wide Solid Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 137. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Wide Solid. BMRX 9013 Wide Solid :30. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 138. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Line. BMLN 9073 Line/Flutter Cut Rev. :30. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 139. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ban Line. BMLN 9053 Line/Flutter Cut :30; BMIC 9095 Aerosol/Flutter Cut :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 140. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Line. BMLN 9053 Line/Flutter Cut :30; Ban Aerosol. BMIC 9095 Aerosol/Flutter Cut :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 141. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ban Line. BMLN 9053 Line/Flutter Cut :30; BMIC 9095 Aerosol/Flutter Cut :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 142. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers Squibb. Ban Wide Solid. BMRX 9013 Wide Solid :30. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 143. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers Squibb. Ban Wide Solid/ BMRX 9025 Wide Solid Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 9)
        - 144. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ban Line. 9053 Line/Flutter Cut :30; BMIC 9095 Aerosol/Flutter Cut :15. 1989 (Box 9)
      - Ban (continued), 1989-1991 (Box 10)
        - 145. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ban. Historical, 1959-1989. 1989 (Box 10)
        - 146. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMBQ 8195 Vignette Alt. Rev. 1 :15. 1989 (Box 10)
        - 147. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Aerosol. BMIC 9105 Aerosol/Flutter Cut Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 10)
        - 148. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Line. BMLN 9073 Line/Flutter Cut :30. 1989 (Box 10)
        - 149. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers Squibb. BMRX 9013 Wide Solid :30; BMRX 9025 Wide Solid Alt :15. 1989 (Box 10)
        - 150. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. BMLN 9073 Line/Flutter Cut Rev. :30; BMIC 9105 Aerosol/Flutter Cut Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 10)
        - 151. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. BMNQ 8195 Vignette Alt. Rev. 1 :15. 1989 (Box 10)
        - 152. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers Squibb. Ban Wide Solid. BMRX 9025 Wide Solid Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 10)
        - 153. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Ban Solid. New Flutter Cut Vers. B mix. BMBQ 9203 Vers. B :30; BMBQ 9215 Lexicon Vers. :15. 1989 (Box 10)
        - 154. Daniel and Charles. Ban Soap. BMBC 9113 Beach House :30 Color. Undated (Box 10)
        - 155. Daniel and Charles. Ban Soap. BMBC 9113 Beach House :30 Color. Undated (Box 10)